dailyworldnewsarticles.com 2013-01-18

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
( _your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs._ )
  * To improve our website  
( _we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you._ )
  * To improve customer service  
( _your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs._ )
  * To process transactions  
( _Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested._ )
  * To send periodic emails  
( _The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions._ )

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.dailyworldnewsarticles.com/legal.html>

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

<http://www.dailyworldnewsarticles.com/contact-us.html>
